{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Entrepreneur",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Week-5",
    "LastModified": "14 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Week-5"
    ]
  },
"quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is a set of controllable and connected variables that a company gathers to satisfy a customer better than its competitor?",
      "answer": "Marketing Mix",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Price",
        "Place",
        "Marketing Mix"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to any goods or services that are produced to meet the consumers' wants, tastes and preferences?",
      "answer": "Product",
      "choices": [
        "Place",
        "Price",
        "Promotion",
        "Product"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What represents the location where the buyer and seller exchange goods or services?",
      "answer": "Place",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Price",
        "Promotion",
        "Place"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is another name for the location where the buyer and seller exchange goods or services?",
      "answer": "Distribution channel",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Price",
        "Promotion",
        "Distribution channel"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What typically buys and stores large quantities of several producers' goods and then breaks into bulk deliveries to supply retailers with smaller quantities?",
      "answer": "Wholesaler",
      "choices": [
        "Retailer",
        "Producer",
        "Consumer",
        "Wholesaler"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a company that buys products from a manufacturer or wholesaler and sells them to end users or customers?",
      "answer": "Retailer",
      "choices": [
        "Wholesaler",
        "Producer",
        "Consumer",
        "Retailer"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is another name for a channel that has no intermediary levels?",
      "answer": "Direct-marketing channel",
      "choices": [
        "Wholesaler",
        "Retailer",
        "Producer",
        "Direct-marketing channel"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the value of money in exchange for a product or service?",
      "answer": "Price",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Place",
        "Promotion",
        "Price"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What pricing strategy is used by businesses to attract customers to a new product or service by offering a lower price during its initial offering?",
      "answer": "Penetration Pricing",
      "choices": [
        "Skimming Pricing",
        "Cost-Plus Pricing",
        "Value-Based Pricing",
        "Penetration Pricing"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the complete set of activities, which communicate the product, brand or service to the user?",
      "answer": "Promotion",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Place",
        "Price",
        "Promotion"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What consists of each person who is involved in the product or service whether directly or indirectly?",
      "answer": "People",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Place",
        "Price",
        "People"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the outside appearance of a product and how it is presented to the customers?",
      "answer": "Packaging",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Place",
        "Price",
        "Packaging"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to a process used by marketers to create an image in the minds of a target market?",
      "answer": "Positioning",
      "choices": [
        "Promotion",
        "Packaging",
        "People",
        "Positioning"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a name, symbol, or other feature that distinguishes a seller's goods or services in the marketplace?",
      "answer": "Brand Name",
      "choices": [
        "Brand",
        "Branding Strategy",
        "Purpose",
        "Brand Name"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the customers' over-all experience of your business?",
      "answer": "Brand",
      "choices": [
        "Brand Name",
        "Branding Strategy",
        "Purpose",
        "Brand"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What branding strategy focuses on financial success and value to the stakeholder?",
      "answer": "Purpose",
      "choices": [
        "Consistency",
        "Emotion",
        "Flexibility",
        "Purpose"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the significance of avoiding things that don't relate to or improve your brand?",
      "answer": "Consistency",
      "choices": [
        "Purpose",
        "Emotion",
        "Flexibility",
        "Consistency"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What branding strategy allows the customers have a chance to feel that they are part of your brand?",
      "answer": "Emotion",
      "choices": [
        "Purpose",
        "Consistency",
        "Flexibility",
        "Emotion"
      ],
      "reference": "Brand",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What branding strategy allows you to adjust and differentiate your approach from your competition?",
      "answer": "Flexibility",
      "choices": [
        "Purpose",
        "Consistency",
        "Emotion",
        "Flexibility"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is equally important for your employees to be well versed in how they communicate with customers and represent the brand of your product?",
      "answer": "Employee Involvement",
      "choices": [
        "Loyalty",
        "Competitive Awareness",
        "Flexibility",
        "Employee Involvement"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an important part of brand strategy that sets the tone for what potential customers can expect?",
      "answer": "Loyalty",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Involvement",
        "Competitive Awareness",
        "Flexibility",
        "Loyalty"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should you not be frightened of and instead take as a challenge to improve your branding strategy?",
      "answer": "Competitive Awareness",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Involvement",
        "Loyalty",
        "Flexibility",
        "Competitive Awareness"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    }
  ]
}